stream-free-movies-online.com 2013-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Viewster

Amended July 22, 2013

VIEWSTER (a trading name of VIEWSTER AG ) recognises that your privacy is very important to you and that it is your right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that trust seriously. VIEWSTER will never sell, rent or, except as set out in this Privacy Policy, otherwise disclose any of your personal information, including your Email address, to any third party without your consent. Unless you give us specific consent to act otherwise, the following policies will govern how VIEWSTER handles the personal information that you provide to us.

##### This Privacy Policy sets out:

  * Collection and use of information
  * Information storage
  * Information sharing and disclosure
  * Security and prevention against loss, misuse or alteration of information
  * Your ability to edit and cancel your account
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Contact details

This Privacy Policy is deemed to be incorporated into the Website Terms and Conditions, which you should read together with this Privacy Policy. Capitalised words used but not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given to them in the Terms and Conditions.

##### Collection and use of information

If you do not register as a Member of VIEWSTER, the information we collect from you is limited. We log your IP address in order to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer this Website and track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may be the same, depending on the type of internet connection. Either way, it would be extremely difficult for us to identify you through your IP address, and we make no attempt to do so. If you reach this Website by clicking on a link or advertisement on another website, then we also log that information. All of this information is collected and used only in aggregate; that is, it is entered into our database, where we can use it to generate overall reports on our visitors, but not reports about individual visitors.

If you choose to register as a Member of VIEWSTER, you will be able to take advantage of all of the features of this Website. VIEWSTER collects some or all of the personally identifiable information set out below when you rent a movie on the VIEWSTER service or register as a Member of VIEWSTER, when you access and use this Website and/or when you use VIEWSTER's Products and/or Services. The information we collect will vary depending on the circumstances, e.g., if you use one of our rental services packages or download film or TV content, we will collect most of this information. If you simply use some of our services, (such as writing a review or entering a competition) we may only collect more limited information.

##### What we collect

  * Full name
  * Email address
  * Information about the films, TV series and other content that you have rented, bought, streamed or downloaded
  * User Material you submit (e.g., your ratings, reviews, user collections, quiz and other user submissions)
  * Information you submit for your User Profile
  * From Facebook, your Facebook user name and profile picture if you choose to use the VIEWSTER Facebook Application

##### We do not collect

  * Your credit card and billing information. This information is collected by our payment process provider. VIEWSTER neither collects nor stores this information.

##### How we use it

  * To recommend other films, TV series and other content that you may like to rent, buy, stream or download
  * To display your favourites list to others
  * To communicate with you regarding your account or purchase of VIEWSTER's Products or Services -related matters
  * To provide you with order and billing history information
  * To contact you about the products and/or services on this Website in which you have expressed an interest
  * To display your User Profile to others users of this Website (in accordance with your security settings)
  * If chosen by you, to allow you to use the VIEWSTER Facebook Application (in accordance with your security settings)
  * To email you offers, news and information
  * To send you samples of, or marketing materials relating to, third party products or services which we believe may be of interest to you. Such materials may accompany the discs you have selected to rent, or may be sent by us separately. Please note that at no time is it necessary for us to provide your personally identifiable information to third parties in order to send you these materials
  * To improve services and enhance personalisation, we may periodically obtain information about you from other third party sources from whom we have lawfully obtained this data and add it to your registration information. Additionally, authorised VIEWSTER personnel may update your registration information to accurately reflect any new information included in any communications received from you.

##### Communication Preferences

If you do not want to receive emails from us with offers, news and information, you can opt out of our newsletter in your "My Account" page.

##### Information storage

All information you provide to us is stored in Switzerland only, on secure servers that are protected in secure facilities, including firewall protection, and located in those countries that form part of the European Economic Area or are considered to provide adequate protection for personal information under the European Union Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC).

##### Cookies

'Cookies' are small text files that are stored by the browser on your computer. Websites are able to read and write these files, which allows them to store things like personalization details and user preferences. We use cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * recognise you as a VIEWSTER member so that we can log you in to this Website on a repeat visit;
  * provide you with customised content and remember preferences you specify while you are using our products or services;
  * deliver advertisements relevant to your interests when you visit our Website and use our products and services;
  * provide general internal and customer analytics to conduct research to improve our Website and our products and services; and
  * support security measures such as requiring re-logging into this Website after a certain amount of time has elapsed.

In addition to our own cookies, we allow certain third parties and affiliates to set and access their cookies on your computer such as companies providing auditing, research and reporting for advertisers. Those parties' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy.

The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our Website essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

##### Third Party Advertising

VIEWSTER works with third party advertising service providers and allows such third parties to target and serve advertising on our Website, and we may use cookies, pixels or other similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable data for use in connection with the delivery of such advertising. You may opt out of receiving third party advertisements from certain companies by visiting the consumer opt-out page of the Network Advertising Initiative located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

##### Information sharing and disclosure

VIEWSTER is committed to protecting your personal information. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except:

  * where VIEWSTER is required by law to disclose information to third parties;
  * where the disclosure is necessary for the performance of our operations (eg. mail delivery, hosting services, protecting us from fraud, and payment of your account); or
  * VIEWSTER buys or sells subsidiaries or business units in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a sale, merger, consolidation or asset sale, or an internal reorganisation, or in the unlikely event of an insolvency. If such a transaction or event required the transfer of customer information, then that information would be one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the commitments made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy or equivalent.

We also may share your personal information with third parties (ie agents or sub-contractors) specifically engaged by VIEWSTER to provide services to us, in which case we will require those parties to keep that information confidential and secure and to use it solely for the purpose of providing the specified services to us.

Companies and individuals registered in the VIEWSTER Affiliate Program receive aggregate information about customers that they direct to VIEWSTER through links on their websites. No personally identifiable information is provided to affiliate members. The information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for the affiliates program and will not be used for general marketing purposes.

VIEWSTER also provides analyses of our customers in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers, movie distributors and other third parties. We do this so that we and our business partners can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you first-rate services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our customers. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific customers.

Linked websites are not under the control of VIEWSTER, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our Website, including Facebook, should you choose to use the VIEWSTER Facebook Application. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website we advise you to examine its terms and conditions of use and privacy policy.

Please note that you have certain rights under the Data Protection Act 1998. You have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you, to correct errors in that information and to prevent VIEWSTER from using your personal information for direct marketing purposes. Should you wish to exercise these rights, or if you have any questions concerning the VIEWSTER privacy policy, contact us using the contact details below.

Security and prevention against loss, misuse or alteration of information

VIEWSTER has implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorised access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.

For transmitting your personal information to us, we use a secure server with a 256-bit SSL certificate from Thwate which encrypts all of your personal information. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorised interception.

While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Your VIEWSTER account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You can play an important role in keeping your personal information secure by maintaining the confidentiality of your password used on the VIEWSTER website. We recommend that you change your password from time to time for additional security. Please advise us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.

Access authorisation is granted only to key VIEWSTER (VIEWSTER AG) staff and to our agents or subcontractors if necessary for the performance of our operations or for them to provide services to us. Any information accessed by those agents or subcontractors is required to be kept confidential and secure and is not permitted to be used for any purpose except to provide their services to us.

Backups are run to prevent loss of information, and our Internet servers are housed in secure facilities.

##### Your ability to edit and cancel your account

You can access the "My account" section from every page on this Website to update and correct the personal details that we gathered when you subscribed and/or when you chose to use any of VIEWSTER's Products or Services. You must be logged in to access this information. All information is password-protected so no one can access the information but you.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, VIEWSTER will review and may edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. VIEWSTER reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy may be amended in accordance with paragraph 1.2 of our Terms and Conditions (of which this Privacy Policy forms part).

##### VIEWSTER's contact details

All correspondence to VIEWSTER regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to:

(Attention: Privacy Officer)  
Viewster AG  
Muhlebachstr. 162  
CH-8008 Zurich

Switzerland  
Email: [info@viewster.com](mailto:info@viewster.com)
